[Music]
hey everybody it's your favorite burping
girl and today we're at the grocery
store
and we're going to be burping on your
groceries
they smell like a good old fart
[Applause]
[Music]
so
my morning coffee is kicking in i'm
gonna have to drop anchor
real soon it's never easy to find a
bathroom at a grocery store
it's usually behind a butcher counter
for some reason
we're probably not allowed to use it in
gilead we can't do
anything except when we need to move the
story along
then somehow we get away with everything
i didn't do anything the old cow i'm off
tom brady but you can call me andrea
nice to meet you are you new yes so
how long have you been making burp
videos a little over a year
why because i'm freaky okay do you only
burp in public
you i burp and i fart i gag and
spit
just everything that's gross with
everybody okay burping girl is a fetish
it's also comedy and it's like the wow
factor
so i cater to all three have you always
been good at burping i'm good at being a
fat girl
oh
do you not eat healthy no what's your
like favorite meal
pizza what kind of quantities are we
talking about like two medium pizzas
yeah i never understand people to buy
two mediums why not just buy two larges
you get 5.99 if you buy two from
domino's domino's pizza
their whole advertising campaign for the
past six years
has been apologizing for how horrible
their pizza is
it's a weird strategy
do you ever say excuse me in your videos
sometimes i do but i don't mean it
i can't guess your age i'm 14.
what 29 but 14 in fetish years
how many fetishes are you into gassy
girl i like foreskin
i like musty boys blow jobs for sure
okay
tell me about your greatest burp sorry
to just
blow over that blow job lord my greatest
burps are the ones that make my eyes
roll back
you ever try harmonizing your burps no
we could do it together
[Applause]
that was music no i'm gonna get sick you
were born
a boy yeah does that take away
some of the allure of being such an
amazing burper people like well of
course you're such a good burper because
most
born females aren't good burpers would
you say that's true
the hormones have taken every
testosterone out of my body so these are
girl burps
have you had a if i did then i wouldn't
be a fetish
have you ever thought of maybe having
the surgery
so that you could get into the queefing
fetish if i had somebody to pay for it
yes
are you dating that can i talk i'm
married to a woman
was she born a woman maybe okay that's
not that's not i don't
sometimes i don't know what questions i
ask are inappropriate if you don't want
to share that that's fine well let's
just say
it's beef but it smells like fish
yeah that is disgusting
[Music]
oh are any of the handmaids wearing
this like this
nasty nasty nasty
nasty nasty
so look at this i mean come on gilead
do you like potatoes not ones that look
like ball sacks now
what's your preferred style of french
fry i like curly
curly is the right answer oh i love a
curly fry
almost makes me uh consider going back
to arby's
that sounds good doesn't it oh i miss
arby's god damn you gilead
who is that gross guy that allows you to
burp in his
mouth in your videos
my ex-boyfriend you want to get back
with me so he'll say he'd do anything
for me
that was so freaking hot
what grosses you out poop poop grosses
you out
i'll poop on somebody i just don't want
nobody to poop on me has there ever been
a video where you're like oh man i wish
i wouldn't have done that
the grocery store video because it went
viral the clip and i was burping on
groceries
on boxes but the internet took it as
i was tampering with food getting my
germs all over it
oh i didn't even look at it that way i
mean but
just just talking over groceries is
gonna get your germs and stuff you don't
eat the box well i don't know
you yeah you get it
let me check my list unlabeled juice i
need a couple potatoes
grab one more thing for my commander we
get out of here
i'm sad
samples jeez
oh they're good
oh gilead just got a little bit spicier
now the trader of joe's is carrying the
new flaming hot doritos
just make sure you wash your hand before
you give your commander a handy
learned that the hard way quick
you have to come with me i'm with the
resistance we're sneaking you across the
border
to canada hannah that i'd rather be
on the wall
yeah canada i love protein birds
i'm so sick of people telling me how
cool toronto is
it sucks
i couldn't help but wonder was canada
even for me or would i miss it here
did i love big or did i just love being
comfortable
oh i'm doing a sex in the city
monologue now
welcome to sex talk with my mom today we
are together
and we're doing
a sperm test because it always comes
down to cam's
premature ejaculation issues
you bring it there people are going to
the butt i'm going into the butt and
enjoying
are you kidding me you're not going to
be the dumb you're going to be the sub
okay mother i will come so quickly
you're just walking down the street just
having coming in your pants
that's a good point but it's not like
you can unbreak a hymen mama
i didn't break the hymen i guess you
could say i learned about prolapsing the
hard way are you talking about the pink
sock
you that's scary it's not just for
germans anymore
mom when was scatting ever for germans
come in hey daniel thanks for coming on
the podcast oh
i've never been asked to be on a podcast
before oh this is so
nice normally guests sit in the chair
over here oh
if this bed could talk guys thank you
for inviting me
into your home lovely welcome where are
you from
chicago originally but we i moved here
two years ago
why i have a boyfriend that lives here
so you have a boyfriend
how does that make your father and
husband feel he was murdered
unfortunately
holy this started off yeah it got
real dark
how far in the past is that i'm not
we're not leaving it just yet
12 years 12 years well i'm horribly
sorry
thank you so you guys have a podcast uh
for people that like to have sex with
their mom no
sex talk with my mom that's in other
words we're opening communication
between children and their parents about
sex do you know a lot of people who want
to have sex with their mother that's
what i was thinking i was like how many
people in this country because you have
a lot of views yeah we have a ton of
viewers and all of them want to have sex
with their mom no
no all of them want to have sex with
your mom no
whose idea was it to do the podcast how
long have you been doing it she wrote a
book called the cougar's guide to
getting your ass back out there you know
and i started youtube channels mainly to
help other women going through being
single again
and it turned out there were just a
bunch of horny guys who like wanted to
know about cougars how did you end up
uh you know with this guy yeah bringing
him into the mix
well i was doing stand-up at the time
uh-huh any red passages out of it this
is from
a chapter called release your inner
stripper
i was like well we're using the same
material why don't we just like
collaborate
are you the only sibling no no they're
two is the other one
uh jealous of your relationship it's a
good question
i don't think either of them really want
that relationship with her you know i
always grew up
my relationship with my mother totally
comfortable
with her making out with my dad or
whatever it never grossed me out
does it bother you to think of your
mother as a sexual person no i would
hope she's just having a robust exercise
yeah more robust than my own actually
all right let's take a few calls okay is
this boy gonna bang his mom or what
the mother and son porn genre is
booming are there offers for you two to
put out a sex tape
no no what type of porn do you like i
like stills on instagram with my exes
do you find that sex has gotten better
as you've
aged absolutely i invented the word
cougar to be a confident older unique
genuine assertive and racy woman
i hate acronyms oh i like that one
though because like you know if you say
cougar you get this image of this
predatory being and
i don't want to think that when i think
of cougar i think of an older woman who
wants to bang younger dudes
that's why i wanted to do the acronym i
know but the acronym's so long i don't
remember one of the letters
confidence and then i've learned to
spell with acronyms which i'm not good
at either
hi uh yeah this is a question for cam
can you talk in a girl's voice i'm
having a real hard time finishing
hey karen how about you let me in your
butt i mean how many topics can there
actually be
to discuss it never ends one guy
actually
offered to have me in a toilet and
he was gonna eat it and he was gonna
give me three grand
when yeah yeah okay so you did that no i
did not what he would you wanted four
grand yes they did what do you think i'm
cheap three grand's not cheap i would
have done it
what do you think your shit's worth
probably a good 50 bucks
have you ever seen your mother naked no
i haven't seen you
maybe when i was a little bit before i
remember looking at my mom's shirt
before i can remember like oh i remember
seeing her nipples were you excited by
that
no but i remember thinking like do all
women's nipples look like that you know
the
the the wait what is this that was a
nipple that was like like like it was
a pinky difference in four kids did you
breastfeed your children only the first
for like six weeks
would you do it now on camera wait for
the offer
i'm gonna bang your mom and make you my
stepson i hope a real cougar attacks you
were you a strict parent no that was a
cool mom i always was scared of cool
moms
why i don't know if that's what you want
to be sometimes don't you want your wife
to be a cool mom nope because a lot of
times i associate the cool mom with like
your friends going like oh yeah i'd hook
up with your mom
because then you feel this weird need to
like like bulk up and like hey man knock
it off with my mom well
so whenever you're showing them because
now you're banging her
you want america's got talent yeah we're
like kind of a choreographed spitting
team
you come from a long line of spitters
are there any topics that are off limits
we didn't need to talk about
your anal experiences as much as we have
i like anal play more than i like the
actual
dick and the ass thing
did not talk about anal experience i
said i like anal play
that's different do you ever like delve
into the world of politics
or finances or any of that stuff nah
except we're talking about finances
in terms of like we need to sell some
vibrators
for me to make rent did you guys have
your own line of vibrators no but i did
get him
and my boyfriend fleshlights you don't
flash like that
is i know what a fleshlight is mother a
fleshlight
all right have you tried one yeah of
course but then
the shame of cleaning it is like it's
like all right
you know what i'll i'll buy a new one
it's the last thing you want to do after
you ejaculate
is clean out this human well i put it in
the dishwasher that's not a bad idea
well i mean ruffina does but regardless
who's that that's my housekeeper your
housekeeper cleans out your fleshlight
in the dishwasher she doesn't know what
it is
thanks for taking my call i think the
podcast is super helpful especially if
you're trying to blast nuts to a hot
milk talking about ass sex
i'd like to apologize that's my immature
fan base they get a little too honest
when you get them all horned up all
right i think it's time to wrap it up
thanks for coming out
thank you was this going to air oh it
just did
how does this podcast work i've got some
bad news for you
in addition to being a huge celebrity
i'm also a volunteer child protective
service agent
boom it's upside down still valid we
don't have sex with each other how many
times do we have to tell you that daniel
okay then explain to me
why you bought this inappropriate
mother's day gift for her
you planted that tell it to the judge
you perverts
take them away boys can i keep that
yes hi guys welcome to my channel i'm dr
sandra lee also known as dr pimple
popper i'm gonna
post blackhead extractions look at that
that's pretty cool cysts being popped i
heard you too much i know i'm starting
to push
push around i'm sorry i made you yell i
know that's why it squirts on you
like home is being removed from the skin
because i know you guys love them and i
love that you love them
enjoy
hey what are you aiming for
[Music]
i think the chiropractor's down the hall
i'm not a hunchback it's a cyst
daniel dr pimple popper will see you now
when did you realize you had a passion
for popping pimples i started to post
popping videos or blackhead extractions
about a year ago on my
instagram and on my youtube channel and
they just got more interest
so i went in and i went and looked and i
saw that there's a
whole community there's a subculture
there always is who just
post popping videos and share them with
each other although your instagram is
very confusing because you have like
normal everyday
like hey this is me out and about sexy
photos next thing is the most
horrific extraction i've ever seen the
goal is to try to get this out of a
smaller little area
okay so a little tightness here okay
how's that okay
not bad right
i'm showing that i'm a real person you
know that i may be a physician and i do
all these surgeries but i'm a girl too
like
you know all my girlfriends i like to
hang out with them i have a husband he
works he's a dermatologist
do patients get upset when they get your
husband and not you yeah
sometimes what type of person likes to
watch
most of them are women i will have to
say i think women love
popping yes they do i had two older
sisters
as a kid oh they couldn't be happier
getting in on me
i do know though that a lot of people
like these videos because they relax
them
they help decrease anxiety they watch
them during panic attacks
they watch it before they go to sleep
none of this is true you're making
that up that is completely horseshit
nobody watches that video and then takes
a nap
i think it's like ready to come like i
need a suction mica
like they do with babies what race of
people has the best skin
it's true that the darker you are the
less likely you are to develop wrinkles
over time
lighter complected people are going to
have more of those fine lines and
wrinkles
so they look older probably sooner than
asians african-americans has hispanics
all of us darker
so you guys win that one category yeah
well we win a couple hours
do you have to talk your patients into
this no not usually in fact
now people come from around the world
i've had people come from london from
saudi arabia for me to pop their zits
are you making more money off your
videos now than you are your practice
no are there people that are watching it
for a
pleasure sexual i'm sure there's people
that watch
anything everything for that but i think
they're in the minority it's not really
a fetish it's more
you know it's like riding a roller
coaster or watching a scary movie i
think it makes people happy
i don't know i i think fetish i think
there's more fetish people in there too
combined with the fact that you're asian
that's a double whammy for a lot of
people
maybe i want to know how nasty these
people are
they aren't nasty they're my patients
and they're absolutely lovely
healthy monsters not at all no why is it
getting that bad
you know the biggest blackheads come
from
older patients who have poor eyesight
who have arthritis in their hands and
they just
are not aware that these things are even
on their skin the big
like growths that we usually see
especially in the nether areas tend to
be men
and i tell them don't worry about it
i've seen a lot of skin tags and then
they pulled on their pants and i had one
guy with like the size of a racquetball
on his butt like on the piece of his
butt this has been going for how long
a number of years yeah okay good
hold on what'd you do with that
disgusting skin tag after you cut it off
i made it into a keychain oh he nazzed a
bit
does anything gross you out recently i
had this woman who
we removed a pylar cyst a big benign
system about this big you know on her
head
and it was soft like it was like kind of
like a balloon but i took it out whole
but when i cut into it afterwards i cut
into it on the table it was like
black mud that came out oh nasty
talk about the smell you know what it
smells like in general it smells like
some of those um more strong cheeses
that's okay so that's not good what's
the worst bodily fluid
i don't know the worst bodily fluid
diarrhea
diarrhea is bad
when the beans come out of people that
i'd lose my mind no you just say oh well
look at that you know that
you got a magic bean in you what's the
closest to the
the butthole that you've ever had to do
an extraction i don't do the butthole
what do you just let him die there's
like pilonidal cysts which occur like
right above the
rectum there but i that's not my domain
i don't do that i'm out
when you see guys naked all the time yes
is it uncomfortable for you at all no
it's not uncomfortable
but i will tell you something funny that
um i used to work with
i worked with other dermatologists who
said that if they were examining a guy
and he
got arrested yeah rousey
oh sorry you're supposed to flick it
that's what you they were doing they
were flicking it
i've never had to do that i know oh
i would be so into that yeah if you
flick a weenie like that like do one of
those
those pops oh if you tuck it back behind
that oh that'll hurt them
okay i'll try that out or make them
finish
this has all been very informative you
know celebrities have been cashing in on
their terrible skin for years
it's time i got in on the action
everyone knows
i have flawless skin but sometimes
before shows
i get a small barely noticeable stress
boil i can't wait
three days for my skin to slightly
improve i
need a more proactive approach that's
why dr pimple popper
is my main squeeze
the first sign of a blemish and i want
all hands on zit
don't stop squeezing until there's blood
on the mirror
thanks to my sexy asian fingers the
results are
instant and the explosive release feels
better than the best
plus a little scarring makes you look
like a man
got this one from a zit this one from a
shark call now and she'll throw in two
biore bacne strips for free
[Music]
when you drink your urine
you become aware of the
absolute need for honesty in all moments
like i said i'm gonna gargle and swish
maybe three
at least three times a day i'm gonna do
a very big
urine treatment i want to
conquer this infection i took ibuprofen
for
ibuprofen and naproxen for a couple of
days
and neither one was really helping
yeah the pain relief and urine therapy
and
not messing around it's amazing
you can't buy anything like
it anyway only you can make it right
lemonade life gives you lemons make
lemonade
lemonade lemonade
hey beat it scumbag it's my turf
everyone knows it
smell your lemonade somewhere else not a
lemonade stand it's the way we stand
oh you nasty hey but if you don't
mind me asking how much you charging
it's free giving away the first taste to
get all the kids hooked
smart why is your pee so dark are you
drinking enough water
i'm drinking enough water okay what made
you want to try it
i was i was desperately
sick uh-huh and it's been sick for years
i was tired of being sick and i was just
like there's got to be something besides
medicine
what kind of sickness do you have if you
don't mind me asking malignant melanoma
in 2004
they gave me a year to live oh wow
yeah cancer and one year into the
treatment you're like i'll try anything
or was it i didn't do their chemo or
anything oh you didn't do it at all
i did the surgery they took 17 lymph
nodes and
found cancer and four of them and you're
like that's enough yep no more surgery
i got to find another way i've had seven
doctors shake my hand and say i've
i need to shake your hand i've never met
anybody that made it through that do
they wash immediately afterwards
[Music]
have you ever had a sandwich yes or
no
no okay i i'm not into that that part of
it what does urine taste like
it depends on what you eat if i eat
asparagus i have to dump it i'm like
you can't drink it you've tried though
asparagus oh yeah
and shrimp shrimp makes it taste like
egg but it doesn't make it smell
different i mean you can't hardly even
stomach it it's so bad
how much do you actually drink i used to
drink about a gallon a day
who pees a gallon a day well the more
you drink the more you get
because it makes it water wetter it
makes the water in your body wetter and
you produce more peat
huh i i don't agree with that at all
explain to me the process of collecting
your pee you've got to catch the
midstream so you let a little go
my mom used to always say that when i
would when i would go take a little
pee tests or whatever you don't pee
first into the toilet then
cut it off which takes practice yeah
that's the pressure okay go on so you're
drinking that clean stuff in the middle
that good clean piss
okay and do you do you every time you
pee do you save it or no yeah you save
it
and then use it for different things you
can
you know put it in a bath and that way
you get it all through your all skin you
know i wouldn't think that that's a good
idea
because pee kind of smells well yeah so
you add a few like lavender essence oils
do you add cream
uh or sugar to your pea or do you take
it yellow straight
i'm a cowboy pee drinker you ever put an
ice cube in it
no because i like it warm you like it
straight from the spigot
from the spigot i can almost reach
the warmth is what i think i would
struggle with the most
if you drink coffee and then drink your
pee
is your pee caffeinated yeah because if
i drink say a shot of vodka
uh-huh you know when i go pee and then
drink it
it tastes like a little like vodka you
get drunk
oh wow in the winter do you eat the
yellow snow that's the good stuff
would you recommend everyone start
drinking their pee even people that
aren't sick
i absolutely would and there's no
scientific proof behind
urine being good for any ailments or is
there
uh there is well you know i don't know
what you would call
scientific well like a scientist came up
with it
um no yeah that's what i thought
oh excuse me daniel i need to use the
restroom well grab a glass
all right so that's an actual glass of
your urine
[Music]
very fresh very fresh
looks pretty dark looks a little dark is
it warm can i feel how warm it is
oh it's a nice temperature it's perfect
and you just drink your pee well no i do
other things with it i drink it through
my eyes
drink it through my ears drink it
through my nose pour it in your eyes
no i use an eye dropper you have an eye
dropper i got one right here i'll show
you
check this out no i'm i'm excited how
much do you put in your eyes
just a drop no i just brown it
like so now there's just pee falling
down on you and you just
lick it off or rub it in does it burn it
burns
is it turning them around a little bit
also it's not good for your eyes
no it's very good it's incred it's
improving my eyesight
yeah and then drink it through your ears
and you know it's like you can go like
this
where do you burn that eye dropper
[Music]
now if i had pee on my hands i would be
a
a little a little grossed out but but
there's pee all over your face right now
and that's okay oh yeah have a sip
do you want me to drink it all not all
of it just a sip
okay that's enough
and you swish with it it cleans your
teeth huh
what about toothpaste i don't really use
it
okay well i'm 100 sold on the benefits
of urine therapy
you're literally sitting on a gold mine
you know who to appreciate this
truckers always making a mess when they
pee into a bottle
hook up a catheter that they could
relieve themselves and clinch their
thirst
for that final push albuquerque and what
about those energy shoes
i bet athletes would really get a jolt
how to sink their teeth into a cube of
congealed kiss
hell i think we could replace gatorade
make pea the official sports drink of
football
this would be a game changer for new
fathers everyone knows there's nothing
stronger than the bond that's created
from a newborn
suckling on a mother's teeth now thanks
to urine
dads can enjoy a similar bonding
experience wait
you want me to do what
guys
what's happening cheers to being a potty
mouth
just gonna wipe off the rim of the glass
so i don't get any
germs
[Applause]
brownie today we're going to demonstrate
how to give a successful blow job
using a banana and two oranges for the
genitalia
now before we get started the first
thing i want to do is put our hair back
in a ponytail that way it doesn't get
the mouth doesn't get in the way
i personally have had only five and a
half
in my life and today we're gonna show
you how to do it really right really
perfect
i was gonna demonstrate how to give a
double blow earlier because
common sense says that if you like one
dick you are going to like to
make some sense but i ate the other
banana okay
you really need your hands and your
mouth going to fill this balls a little
bit
show him the passion show him that you
loved it going to keep your eyes shut
for the most part
but every once in a while go ahead and
look up at them yeah like that
yeah that looks pretty guys
[Music]
[Applause]
hey hey hey you blow it you buy it oh
hello daniel we're brownley
thought i recognized you listen uh
welcome to my stand
everything here is farm to butthole
you're welcome to anything
didn't know we had a celebrity visiting
us my first
question is what the is on your
face
it's mechanical paint so you do it
yourself yes
every morning just on my days off when
i'm not working
okay so you're not allowed to wear
satanic war paint to work not at the
cereal factory
that's a cereal factory yes that makes
it real what kind of cereal
a lot of granola stuff what milk do you
like for your cereal when you have
cereal two percent
why not just go to skim i don't like
soft dash
okay warped brownly now is that your
given name
i got that name for my ex-girlfriend she
said i was warped
because i want to have sex with other
people i like the fact that she like
overlooked all
of this nonsense and went with the fact
that you just want to sleep with other
people
yes we're still friends though okay so
she is alive oh she's alive
i've been meaning to ask you what's the
story about the video
where you were that stuffed bear
the teddy bears become legendary
sure all around eugene oregon just
because of the videos because i do it
live too
this week actually they're having a
meeting at my work about sexual
harassment
involving videos and i can't be there
but you're not allowed to be there
no because i'm here oh so everyone has
to watch go through this meeting
except me well that's probably good that
you're not there it'll allow a lot of
the staff that's terrified of you to
speak freely
did we pat you down no jesus
they say this look is called lumber
sexual
i think it's pretty satanic when you use
the word satanic what does it mean
well what do you think worshiping the
devil no
no not in traditional sense no okay so
what does it mean
you don't understand no i don't uh like
like does it mean cool
good me yeah cooler the bomb or the bomb
all right i get it i i do understand it
yeah
satanic style satanic style you want to
get that going
oh it's going what time you go to bed at
night
i get late like 10 30. no
i go to bed like at four in the morning
okay i work late at cereal factory but
then i need time to
take go to bars after work and do some
karaoke
satanic style what kind of satanic style
karaoke songs are you picking
i'll do some rap songs to open up loosen
up the crowd sure back out
they're not gonna see that coming back
that ass up oh yeah juvenile
uncensored i will say the word well i
mean technically you're halfway
some people would watch a video of you
blowing a fruit or teaching people how
to give a and think that's gay
your thoughts you know what if you
listen to video
if you listen to it it's obvious i'm
straight of course but no one listens
that's cause they're too busy jerking
off i said in the video i said i've only
had
five and a half i haven't gave five and
a half i've never gave in a
yeah you took to it like a duck to water
would you clarify what a half is
yeah well it's when uh the girl is
blowing you and she passes out before
she finishes
nah in time the meds right yeah
um how fast could you get a guy off if
you had to
you saw the video what do you think i
finished before you started
the hand is the key that's the main part
hand the girls don't realize that the
hands doing all the heavy lifting
i've had girls that just use their mouth
and really pisses me off
how far can you take this down my deep
throating skills aren't great
i don't know i challenge you
sorry i don't know who won here i gotta
sell this man
bj's are all well and good but let me
show you how to satisfy a lady
i like to use a pomegranate because it's
a red
and gross and kind of confusing
just like a lady's cod
well you get the idea
or if there's something i've been
meaning to ask you would you ever
consider new horn
that'd be really satanic all right
it's odd that you had that on the tip of
your tongue
[Music]
hello did someone order some wet
juicy fruit on a stick
[Music]
hey goldilocks you're gonna take this or
what fine this is going up your ass
isn't it
[Music]
[Applause]
who's here sorry to bug again but that
edible arrangement was for your neighbor
okay i am positive i didn't give you
anything chocolate covered
get my mister out and good
as new take this for myself
mary winchenbach runs turdy works it's
art made from the stuff that moose leave
behind
the terms that i use to name these
products are everyday terms that people
are used to hearing and what we did see
is we took them turns and we crammed
them in between the number there so
that's 132 330.
that's just one of many products she
offers now over here we make fecal
people
and depending upon the shape of their
middle turds right there we can do with
big boobs or guts or butts or long legs
are short like see because there's no
two turrets that are ever like
you ever seen the two turds alike
i've got a one-of-a-kind peter dinklage
dookie right here it's half off
don't all turds look like peter dinklage
i got chris pratt scat i got the guy
from rudy's duty and mamma mia i even
got meryl streep's diarrhea but the real
prize this baby right here
a whopper from emma watson wait there's
two celebrity poop booths
wow that's my brother okay he sells
turds that look like
celebrities i'm selling their actual
brown gold here that's half brother
your mom's a
mary how's business hey great how you
doing mind if i pull up a stool pull up
a stool
pun intended all right mary where are
you from
i am from maine where in maine
somerville maine can i smell your
fingers
you see you can if you want oh
okay that is question number two
now let's get to this nonsense first of
all why do you spell turds with an
i i think that webster's dictionary has
it wrong i think that someone didn't
think it out real good because if you
look at the word bird it's b-i-r-d
so bird turd so it should be spelled
t-i-r-d
you smoke marijuana yes
i do how'd you know we have some
products that relate to that too
like what we have a clip oh that's
a good idea yes and you put a joint on
that and pass that around
how long have you been uh dealing with
these moose turds been doing it about 15
years
really yes just so i know how many
pellets are in a single dropping for a
moose
they'll typically out two to four
hundred turns every time they take a
dump
that's gonna feel amazing oh it's
exciting you know and it's like ching
ching
i mean you watch the turds come out of
their ass and it's like 5 10 15 20. it's
like
playing wheel of fortune slot mission
exactly typically we'll get 100
to 150 pounds of turds every time we go
out in the woods
you know we put them in bags and sling
them over the shoulder and drag them out
and by the time we get out we're pooped
okay yes now how fresh will you grab
them
i like them as fresh and juicy as i can
get them the longer they sit in the
woods they'll get punky
and dried out you know and that kind of
compromises the product integrity so to
speak
doesn't seem primed oh that's nice do
you use hand sanitizer
good to know
no our turds are good you need to go out
in the woods with us collecting turds
someday i don't want to collect turds
we could violate you out of the woods
violate me
seems insane where do you sell all this
stuff we sell it at craft fairs
online he's ordered online yep is it
legal to mail poop
it is the products are non-hazardous
essentially you could eat it have you
ever tasted one
i've put one in my mouth before did you
bite down
a little bit do you
coat the turds or well yeah we have two
different kinds of coatings we use
because some people like a natural
looking turd and some people like it
when their turds glisten
oh you know because we want to please
everyone it's nice of you only moose
no we have cow turds too oh really yes
we have a couple right there and one of
what we call a and the other
one we call a kawadunga so you just put
a turd on a piece of wood
yeah that's not a product whether
you make uh turd candles turd candles
too it's a little earthy
we actually have a scratch and sniff
area right there to validate the fact
that our don't stink
do you ever think he'd outgrow poop
jokes no
it's only getting worse with age what's
your best seller the poo poo clocks
and the fecal people oh my god the fecal
people
yes now depending upon the shape of
their middle turds right there we can do
them with the big boobs or guts or butts
or long legs or short legs why can't
these
the fecal people be genderless they are
genderless oh nice but we did develop a
couple fecal people down here that do
have gender arnold we did
little deer turds for the for the
boobies and for the ding dong and stuff
those are going to go on top of wed cake
oh that's nice yes that's where they
should go a wedding cake
okay the dart board it's that's just
that's a crap shoot
you just wrap some velcro around
absolutely it's brilliant
it's not brilliant it is people love
that why would they buy that why don't
they just go do it themselves
for it this is what i wanted to show you
right here
the key chains see now due to the high
fiber diet of a moose the turds float
yeah you ever drop the key in the water
you're going to look for a floating turd
and then key is going to be dangling
right underneath that turd well it
depends on how many keys you have well
you have to cram an extra turn on if you
get a lot of keys
like a janitor they would they would
have to have exactly a power dump
so you're saying with the keychain you
just keep poop in your pocket absolutely
have you ever used human no
oh gross that's gross did human turds i
wouldn't touch a human turd
and they probably don't even float some
do well i'm not gonna go around
figuring that out i'll let you worry if
i'm touching that
how often do you get pinkeye i've never
had pink eye you know you pink eye from
human poop
i've never is that is that actually how
you get pink eye from getting
poop in your eye so you can get it from
any kind of poop though that would be
like a shitty idea one day a shitty idea
we have that it's right here there's
little turds in that deer i right there
that's a shitty idea
come on what is this is half-assed well
what do you say
it's just a it's a turd this is
tape
i know you can't sell this no i don't
sell it that's one of my props you know
you're kind of like a like gallagher
what's this go for 15 bucks how much
does the tray cost without poop in it
20. that's a poo-poo platter i mean the
tray alone
if i scraped all this poop out it's a
nice good tray i'm starting to
understand
your business model what you're doing is
taking existing products and gluing
turds to them
it's brilliant thank you i have a few
ideas of how we can expand your brand
excellent what do you got what about
poop poles hardware for all your kitchen
cabinets
instantly devalue your home socks
socks yeah take your socks okay
film with moose turds throw in the
microwave
30 to 45 seconds then when your foot
goes in oh it's gonna feel so nice and
warm
and soft how about frozen diarrhea cubes
now
your cocktails won't get watered down by
normal ice
that's a good idea too thank you by the
way any idea that i give you
is 100 yours free and clear
all right i saved my biggest and
shittiest idea for last we take the
greenest car on the road
and make it brown i'm calling it the
turd tesla model bm
isn't she abused yes she is only need a
thousand dollars to pre-order
estimated delivery of five years what's
the cost it's the price of a regular
tesla plus poops and labor
[Applause]
you